const data = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT needed before bringing a cat home?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Litter box & Litter",
      "Interactive toys",
      "Cat Food",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Catnip",
  },

  {
    question:
      "Cats do not require much care and human companionship, true or false?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "True",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "False",
  },
  {
    question: "When you cat proof your home, what is the maximum gap you can allow?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "2.5 inches",
      "3 inches",
      "1 inch"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "1.5 inches",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I cat proof my house if I have a balcony?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["don't open balcony door, just be careful"],
    correctAnswer: "install a safety net",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following are NOT approved ways to cat proof your house?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "DIY mesh with cable ties",
      "Reinforce solutions for windows & grills",
      "Invisible grills with <= 1.5 inch gap",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Magnetic screen or mosquito mesh",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following are NOT benefits of sterilizing a cat?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Reduce undesirable behaviour (eg: aggression, running away)",
      "Improve physical & mental health of the cat",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "there are no benefits",
  },
  {
    question: "Do you need to bring your cat to the vet when you first bring it home?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Nope"],
    correctAnswer: "Yes",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following are suitable diets for your cat?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Dry kibble only with free flow of water",
      "Wet food with no water",
      "Anything is fine as long as it isnt poisonous",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Sufficient protein and ample water",
  },
  {
    question: "What should I do if my cat is not eating?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "Force feed",
      "Dont do anything",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Try change food and if it doesnt work, see a vet",
  },
  {
    question: "How many litter boxes should you have?",
    incorrectAnswers: [
      "1 per cat",
      "1 per room",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "2 per cat",
  }
];

export default data;